Input: learning topic — Linear transformations and matrices
Input: TeachingVideoAgent.__init__ — output_dir, assets_dir, reference mapping
Planner: get_prompt1_outline — outline prompt
Planner: generate_outline — outline.json
Planner: get_prompt2_storyboard — storyboard prompt
Planner: _enhance_storyboard_with_assets — storyboard_with_assets.json
Coder: generate_storyboard — Section objects
Coder: get_prompt3_code — Manim code prompt
Coder: generate_codes — section .py files
Render: debug_and_fix_code — section mp4
Critic: get_mllm_feedback and optimize_with_feedback — optimized section video
Output: merge_videos — Linear_transformations_and_matrices.mp4